I'm going to be honest. Recently, it has
felt like I've been holding back on my
YouTube channel. It's not intentional,
but I want to change that now to 10x the
value that I'm providing to you through
my content. It's actually really
exciting to me. So, I want to dive into
that with you now, including two big
changes for my channel. First, I'm going
to be uploading once a week now instead
of twice a week. And along with that,
I'm going to very much be increasing the
quality of my videos by really leaning
into what makes me stand out as an AI
content creator and educator. And so
we'll dive into what all that means.
This is going to be very much raw
footage right now. I just want to give
you a quick transparent update for
things that are changing, things that
I'm very excited about as well. Now,
here's the thing. I started my YouTube
channel about 11 months ago. And that
entire time, I stuck with the exact same
schedule. Two videos a week, every
Sunday and Wednesday at 7:00 Central
time. And obviously, that consistency
has served me very well. My channel has
exploded over the last 11 months to
something I could have even dreamed of
when I began. And I'm very grateful for
that. But it is time for that schedule
to change. When you first start your
YouTube channel, it makes sense to focus
a lot on quantity. And I was very much
doing that with two videos a week. It's
how you learn really fast, see what
works, and just get your ideas out there
on the internet. That's what I did. But
once you establish your initial
audience, and I very much feel like I've
done that, it makes sense to shift more
to focus on the quality of videos. So
less content, but the videos that I do
want to put out, I want them to be
extremely high quality, like 10x the
value of all the other videos I've been
putting out at this point. And that's
what I want to do for you now. And going
down to one video a week is definitely
going to make that possible. You have no
idea how many amazing ideas I've had for
content that I haven't gotten around to
doing yet. simply because of how long it
would take to make that video. I'm
talking full master classes, diving into
rag strategies and combining them
together. Building AI agents from start
to finish and truly productionizing
them. Taking my open source projects to
the next level like Archon and the local
AI package. Those are the kind of things
that I want to really invest into now.
Spending 20, 25 hours per video. And
that's what I can do going down to one a
week because I already spend at least 10
hours per video doing two a week right
now. And I really feel like even aside
from having more time, I feel like I
have more skills to make that happen
now. Especially building out the AI
agent mastery course for the Dynamis
community, I have pushed my skills to
the next level. I really gone to that
next level, being able to make this kind
of super highquality content for you to
really make me stand apart so that every
single video I can have on my channel
will give you a substantial benefit to
your AI journey. That's the goal that I
have for you now. And don't worry if you
like my content right now and you get a
lot out of it. It's going to remain that
way. It's not this kind of substantial
shift where I'm completely reinventing
the things that I focus on. It really is
just upping the quality and going deeper
in the things that I already cover for
you. So for example, if I were to build
on an AI agent in a 20-minute video
right now, I might turn it into a
40minute video where I actually show you
how to bring the agent into a production
environment. So, same kind of topic,
same things that will apply to you and
resonate with you, but just going at a
deeper level to make sure you really
have what it takes to build AI agents
with big impact that are production
ready. So, I hope that makes sense. I
really don't want to sway you away from
watching my content. I want this to be a
10x in value for you. And I still very
much want to have my same introductory
shorter content as well, introducing you
to new agent frameworks or tools or ways
to build agents. But I definitely want
to now combine that with my super
highquality content that takes a lot of
prep on my part. Having a really good
balance there to really make my channel
stand out for you. And that actually
brings me to the last thing that I want
to talk to you about, which is the
reason behind me doing this kind of
reinventing of myself and my channel.
Cuz here's the thing. Over the past few
months, there has been an explosion of
AI content creators on YouTube. And I
don't want to call them competition. I
respect a ton of them. I have a personal
relationship with some of them. I've
supported many of them directly. I don't
want to call them competition, but
viewership is split between these
different content creators. And I've
seen across the board, viewership is
just kind of a tough thing to manage
right now for any content creator in the
AI space. And so, what I want to do is
really make myself stand apart. I think
as viewership gets split, it just
becomes even more and more important
over time to really lean into what makes
me stand out over other people in the AI
space. Not that you would watch me
exclusively, but that there would be a
continuous reason for you to come to me
along with any other content creators
that you watch. And I have been thinking
about this a lot over the past couple of
months and getting a lot of feedback
from you guys on YouTube and then also
in my Dynamis community of what makes me
stand out. And I've really landed on
what that is. It all goes back to my
motto that I share on YouTube and in my
Dynamis community all of the time.
Capabilities, not tools. That's what I
try so hard to lean into with everything
that I teach. And here's what I mean by
that. You and I and everyone who is
learning about generative AI is doing it
to solve a specific problem or maybe
multiple problems. And no matter what
you are building for yourself or your
business, the most important thing is
the capabilities that you are building,
not the underlying tools that you are
using. And I see so many people get
super married to using specific tools
when they're building AI agents and
other things with generative AI. And
that is so dangerous because of how fast
the AI landscape is evolving. If you get
super sucked into using a specific tool
and you spend thousands and thousands of
hours mastering it, you never know when
that tool is going to become irrelevant.
And I guarantee it will get to the point
where you're using a tool that is not
optimal for the problem just because
you're so married to using it. And so
when I talk about capabilities, I'm
talking about learning the higher
leverage skills that transcend any
individual tool you could be using.
Things like design patterns and
architecture, the systems that go into
building AI agents, and the best
practices, what it takes to build a
truly production ready AI agent. These
are the kind of skills that you should
put most of your time into learning
that, like I said, transcend the
individual tools you could be using. So
learning tools is good. You need to do
it and that's why I focus on it somewhat
on my channel. But then learning
capabilities and these higher leverage
skills is great. That's where more of
your time should be put. And that's what
I focus on so much on my channel. I want
to keep doing that even more with this
new kind of content that I want to
create for you. Like for example, when I
say building an AI agent from start to
finish, I literally mean having like a
one and a half hour or 2hour video where
I go from planning an agent to
prototyping it to building it out in
code with an AI coding assistant and
containerizing it and deploying it and
securing it and scaling it, going
through that entire process, picking
certain tools along the way, but showing
you the kind of design decisions and
what goes on in my head as I build these
agents really make it so that you can
follow along. Use that exact same
process for anything that you want to
build. Building a system that can scale,
that can work with any tools that you
have. You learn the things to take your
agents that far. That is my goal for
you. So, in summary, I'm moving down to
one video a week to 10x the quality of
my content for you, especially cuz I'll
be leaning more into what really makes
me stand out, which is my emphasis on
capabilities over tools. Really helping
you learn what it takes to build
production ready AI agents to have a big
impact with AI. not just building toys
or simple automations. That's what I've
got for you. And I'm kicking it off
actually this Wednesday with a local AI
master class which I cannot wait for.
Already going to be providing a lot more
value to you with that. So I hope you're
looking forward to that. And with that,
I will see you in the next